[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these statements is true about the Seahorse?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["The male Seahorse has a brooding pouch on the front side of his body.", "The male and the female stay together for life.", "The female produces dozens to thousands of eggs."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following octopi has the scientific name Enteroctopus Dofleini?", "correct_answer": "Giant Pacific Octopus", "incorrect_answers": ["None of these", "Common Octopus", "Blue Ringed Octopus"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who was the first Chinese writer to win the Nobel Prize for Literature?", "correct_answer": "Gao Xingjian", "incorrect_answers": ["Xia Zhinian", "Choi Chi Fung", "Cai Zhifeng"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does the name of the Chinese salad Yusheng mean?", "correct_answer": "Raw fish", "incorrect_answers": ["Sweet salad", "Slimy shrimp", "Sour salad"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What condition is characterized by fear of strangers?", "correct_answer": "Xenophobia", "incorrect_answers": ["Dendrophobia", "Dystychiphobia", "Claustrophobia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This countrys national holidays include:\n- Independence Day, 10 December (date of independence from Spain, 1898) \n- 20 May (independence from US administration, 1902)\n- Rebellion Day 26 July (1953)", "correct_answer": "Cuba", "incorrect_answers": ["Chile", "Mexico", "Palestine"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what European city are Piazza San Marco and Canale Grande located?", "correct_answer": "Venice", "incorrect_answers": ["Lisbon", "Madrid", "Florence"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Due to Silicons similarity with Carbon, some scientists have proposed the possibility of Silicon-based life. Which popular TV production propagated the idea?", "correct_answer": "Star Trek", "incorrect_answers": ["The Day the Earth Stood Still", "The X files", "Close Encounters of the Third Kind"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In which of these movies does Thomas Lennon portray a ping-pong player?", "correct_answer": "Balls of Fury", "incorrect_answers": ["Good Luck Chuck", "The Invisible", "Eden Court"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which natural satellite is Jupiters largest moon as well as the largest moon in the whole Solar System?", "correct_answer": "Ganymede", "incorrect_answers": ["Titan", "Io", "Europa"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was Beyonces first hit?", "correct_answer": "Dangerously in Love", "incorrect_answers": ["Take Me as I Am", "Ring  the Alarm", "Let Go"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This cult English crime film, about a heist gone wrong, was Guy Richies first feature-length movie.", "correct_answer": "Lock, Stock and Two Smoking Barrels", "incorrect_answers": ["Human Traffic", "Gang War", "Cast Away"]}]